kewlshare.com 2015-10-30

# pp

## Privacy Policy

OutBeast operates several websites including Outbeast.com It is OutBeast’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, OutBeast collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. OutBeast’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how OutBeasts visitors use its website. From time to time, OutBeast may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

OutBeast also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. OutBeast only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to OutBeast’s websites choose to interact with OutBeast in ways that require OutBeast to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that OutBeast gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at Outbeast.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with OutBeast – by purchasing access to our service, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, OutBeast collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with OutBeast. OutBeast does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

### Aggregated Statistics

OutBeast may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. OutBeast may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, OutBeast does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

OutBeast discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on OutBeast’s behalf or to provide services available at OutBeast’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using OutBeast’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. OutBeast will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, OutBeast discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when OutBeast believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of OutBeast, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an OutBeast website and have supplied your email address, OutBeast may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with OutBeast and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. OutBeast takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. OutBeast uses cookies to help OutBeast identify and track visitors, their usage of OutBeast website, and their website access preferences. OutBeast visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using OutBeast’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of OutBeast’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If OutBeast, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that OutBeast goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of OutBeast may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by OutBeast and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, OutBeast may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in OutBeast’s sole discretion. OutBeast encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have an Outbeast.com account, you should also check your feed for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
